/* eslint-disable import/no-anonymous-default-export */
const questionBank = [
  {
    question:
      "The first and only Nigeria to play for more than two football teams in champions leagues?",
    answers: [
      "Emmanuel Amunike",
      "Finidi George",
      "Taribo West",
      "Kanu Nwankwo",
    ],
    correct: "Taribo West",
    questionId: "51",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which nigerian has the highest appearances in uefa champions league?",
    answers: ["Finidi George", "Victor Moses", "Mikel Obi", "Kanu Nwankwo"],
    correct: "Kanu Nwankwo",
    questionId: "52",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which nigerian has the highest number of goals in uefa champions league?",
    answers: [
      "yakubu Aiyegbeni",
      "finidi George",
      "Obafemi Martins",
      "Kanu Nwankwo",
    ],
    correct: "Obafemi Martins",
    questionId: "53",
  },
  {
    question: "With 131goals ,who is the goalkeeper all-time topscorer?",
    answers: [
      "Johnny Vegas Fernández",
      "José Luis Chilavert",
      "Rogério Ceni",
      "René Higuita",
    ],
    correct: "Rogério Ceni",
    questionId: "54",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The only footballer to have worn the number 9 jersey and scored for Nigeria at the FIFA WorldCup?",
    answers: [
      "Odion Ighalo",
      "Obafemi Martins",
      "Rashidi Yekinni",
      "Emmanuel Emenike",
    ],
    correct: "Rashidi Yekinni",
    questionId: "1",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The only player in history to have won three FIFA World Cup(1958,1962 and 1970)?",
    answers: ["Diego Maradona", "Ronaldo De Lima", "Romario", "Pelè"],
    correct: "Pelè",
    questionId: "2",
  },
  {
    question:
      "They youngest player ever to have scored a hat-trick in a FIFA World Cup match?",
    answers: [
      "Pelè",
      "Alfredo De Stefano",
      "Ronaldo De Lima",
      "Marco Van Basten",
    ],
    correct: "Pelè",
    questionId: "3",
  },
  {
    question: "The highest goal scorer for the Nigerian national team?",
    answers: [
      "Rashidi yekinni",
      "Segun odegbami",
      "yakubu aiyegbeni",
      "obafemi martins",
    ],
    correct: "Rashidi yekinni",
    questionId: "4",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The only player who have played in three different world for three different countries (yugoslavia,serbia and Montenegro,serbia)?",
    answers: [
      "Milan Jovanovic",
      "Dejan Stankovic",
      "Savo Milošević",
      "Milenko Ačimovič",
    ],
    correct: "Dejan Stankovic",
    questionId: "5",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player has played the most matches at the WorldCup excluding qualifying?",
    answers: [
      "Miroslav Klose",
      "Paolo Maldini",
      "Rafeal Màrquez",
      "Lothar Matthäus",
    ],
    correct: "Lothar Matthäus",
    questionId: "6",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player scored the fastest hat-trick in the Premier League?",
    answers: ["Didier Drogba", "Mohammed Salah", "Sadio Mane", "Thierry Henry"],
    correct: "Sadio Mane",
    questionId: "7",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who scored the fastest goal in Premier League history,came in 7.69 seconds?",
    answers: ["Emily heskey", "Alan shearer", "sadio mane", "Shane Long"],
    correct: "Shane Long",
    questionId: "8",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team won the first Premier League title?",
    answers: [
      "Arsenal fc",
      "Manchester United",
      "Blackburn rovers",
      "Chelsea fc",
    ],
    correct: "Manchester United",
    questionId: "9",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which country has appeared in three World Cup finals,but never won the competition?",
    answers: ["Netherlands", "Czechoslovakia", "Germany", "Croatia"],
    correct: "Netherlands",
    questionId: "10",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Messi wore the No.30 at the start of his Barca career and is now No.10. What other number has he worn for the club?",
    answers: ["No 31", "No 19", "No 10", "No 11"],
    correct: "No 19",
    questionId: "21",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Ronaldo helped Portugal win the European Championship in which year?",
    answers: ["2004", "2016", "2012", "2019"],
    correct: "2016",
    questionId: "22",
  },
  {
    question: "Which club has won the most uefa Champions League titles?",
    answers: ["AC Milan", "Real Madrid", "Liverpool", "Bayern Munich"],
    correct: "Real Madrid",
    questionId: "23",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is the only player to win the uefa Champions League with three different clubs?",
    answers: ["Samuel eto'o", "deco", "Clarence Seedorf", "Christiano Ronaldo"],
    correct: "Clarence Seedorf",
    questionId: "24",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Three people to have won the Champions League a record three times as manager?",
    answers: [
      "Alex Ferguson,Carlo Ancelotti and Zinedine Zidane",
      "Jose mourinho,Carlo Ancelotti and Vicente del Bosque",
      "Bob Paisley,Carlo Ancelotti and Zinedine Zidane",
      "Carlo Ancelotti,Zinedine Zidane and Jupp Heynckes",
    ],
    correct: "Bob Paisley,Carlo Ancelotti and Zinedine Zidane",
    questionId: "25",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which season was the European Cup rebranded as the Uefa Champions League?",
    answers: ["1992-93", "1991-92", "1990-91", "1989-90"],
    correct: "1992-93",
    questionId: "26",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team was the first from the UK to win the European Cup?",
    answers: ["Nottingham forest", "Liverpool", "Celtic", "Aston Villa"],
    correct: "Celtic",
    questionId: "27",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The uefa Champions League has been won only once by a team from Romania which is?",
    answers: ["CFR Cluj", "Steaua Bucharest", "victuria", "Astra"],
    correct: "Steaua Bucharest",
    questionId: "28",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the Champions Leagues top goal scorer of alltime?",
    answers: [
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Lionel Messi",
      "Zlatan ibrahimovic",
      "Raul Gonzalez",
    ],
    correct: "Cristiano Ronaldo",
    questionId: "29",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for most Champions League winners medals?",
    answers: [
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Lionel Messi",
      "Sergio Ramos",
      "Francisco Gento",
    ],
    correct: "Francisco Gento",
    questionId: "30",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of this player spent time playing in Laliga,premier league,and have been crowned African Footballer of the Year four times and the African Cup of Nation twice?",
    answers: [
      "Micheal essien",
      "Emmanuel adebayo",
      "Samuel Eto'o",
      "yaya toure",
    ],
    correct: "Samuel Eto'o",
    questionId: "41",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Singer in Irish boyband Westlife Nicky Byrne played for which preimiership teams before moving into music?",
    answers: ["Oxford united", "Millwall", "Leeds United", "burnley fc"],
    correct: "Leeds United",
    questionId: "42",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the total number of goals scored in Uruguay 1930 FIFA WorldCup?",
    answers: ["20 goals", "75 goals", "70 goals", "65 goals"],
    correct: "70 goals",
    questionId: "43",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the country has the highest FIFA WorldCup titles?",
    answers: ["Germany", "Italy", "Uruguay", "Brazil"],
    correct: "Brazil",
    questionId: "44",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of Former Brazilian,who played in Laliga,seria A, and spent time in prison after being found to have used a fake passport?",
    answers: ["Ronaldinho", "Rivaldo", "Ronaldo", "Romario"],
    correct: "Ronaldinho",
    questionId: "45",
  },
  {
    question:
      "With 202 cleansheets,which goalkeeper has the best record in the English Premier League?",
    answers: ["De Gea", "David seaman", "Petr Cech", "Joe hart"],
    correct: "Petr Cech",
    questionId: "46",
  },
  {
    question: "With 260 goals,who is the Premier Leagues all-time top scorer?",
    answers: ["Thierry henry", "Alan Shearer", "Wayne Rooney", "Robbie Fowler"],
    correct: "Alan Shearer",
    questionId: "47",
  },
  {
    question: "What year did George Obong weah won ballon d'or?",
    answers: ["1992", "1995", "1994", "1993"],
    correct: "1994",
    questionId: "48",
  },
  {
    question: "Who has the most appearances in the Uefa Champions League?",
    answers: ["Lionel Messi", "C.ronaldo", "Iker Casillas", "Gainluigi buffon"],
    correct: "Iker Casillas",
    questionId: "49",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The first ever player to score,when the European Cup renamed to UEFA champions league?",
    answers: [
      "Marco van basten",
      "Diego maradona",
      "Daniel Amokachi",
      "George weah",
    ],
    correct: "Daniel Amokachi",
    questionId: "50",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which outfield player appeared in the Champions League final in three different decades?",
    answers: [
      "Ryan Giggs",
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Lionel Messi",
      "Sergio Ramos",
    ],
    correct: "Ryan Giggs",
    questionId: "31",
  },
  {
    question:
      "With nine goals,who scored the most goals in a single European Championship tournament?",
    answers: [
      "Fernando Torres",
      "Marco van basten",
      "Miroslav Klose",
      "Michel Platini",
    ],
    correct: "Michel Platini",
    questionId: "32",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which year did the European Championship expand from 16 teams to 24 teams?",
    answers: ["Euro 2012", "Euro 2016", "Euro 2004", "Euro 2008"],
    correct: "Euro 2016",
    questionId: "33",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Euro 2000 final between France and Italy was decided by Golden Goal.Which player scored the goal?",
    answers: [
      "Francesco Totti",
      "Thierry henry",
      "Fillipo inzaghi",
      "David Trezeguet",
    ],
    correct: "David Trezeguet",
    questionId: "34",
  },
  {
    question: "FC Cologne have which animal on their club crest?",
    answers: ["A cow", "A bird", "A shark", "A goat"],
    correct: "A goat",
    questionId: "35",
  },
  {
    question: "Which Football club is associated with Galacticos?",
    answers: ["Leeds United", "Real Madrid", "LA Galaxy", "Olympiakos fc"],
    correct: "Real Madrid",
    questionId: "36",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Manchester United famously wearred,but what colours did they wear before adopting red?",
    answers: [
      "black and red",
      "blue and green",
      "black and gold",
      "Green and gold",
    ],
    correct: "Green and gold",
    questionId: "37",
  },
  {
    question: "Which club is sometimes referred to as FC Hollywood?",
    answers: ["La Galaxy", "Chelsea fc", "Bayern Munich", "Celtic"],
    correct: "Bayern Munich",
    questionId: "38",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In Spanish football,The award given to topscorer 'the Pichichi' is named after who?",
    answers: [
      "Enzo 'Pichichi' Moreno",
      "Rafael 'Pichichi' Moreno",
      "Rafael 'Pichichi' Montoya",
      "Suarez 'Pichichi' alonso",
    ],
    correct: "Rafael 'Pichichi' Moreno",
    questionId: "39",
  },
  {
    question: "Which MSL franchise team does David Beckham own?",
    answers: [
      "Inter Miami",
      "FC Dallas",
      "New England revolution 2",
      "LA Galaxy 2",
    ],
    correct: "Inter Miami",
    questionId: "40",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which WorldCup did Diego Maradona score his infamous'Hand of God' goal?",
    answers: ["Italy 1990", "Spain 1982", "Mexico 1986", "Argentina 1978"],
    correct: "Mexico 1986",
    questionId: "11",
  },
  {
    question: "The record number of WorldCup goals is 16, scored by who?",
    answers: ["Pelè", "Ronaldo de lima", "Harry kane", "Miroslav Klose"],
    correct: "Miroslav Klose",
    questionId: "12",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the two English players to have won the WorldCup GoldenBoot?",
    answers: [
      "Gary lineker & Harry kane",
      "Harry Kane & Michael owen",
      "Gary lineker & Emily heskey",
      "Harry Kane & David Beckham",
    ],
    correct: "Gary lineker & Harry kane",
    questionId: "13",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Name of the former Germany international who went on to become a professional wrestler in the WWE?",
    answers: ["Kevin kuranyi", "Tim Wiese", "Oliver kahn", "sukuta paso"],
    correct: "Tim Wiese",
    questionId: "14",
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which Spanish clubs nickname is Los Colchoneros, which translates to English as "The Mattress Makers"?',
    answers: ["Atletico bilbao", "Getafe", "Atletico Madrid", "Granada"],
    correct: "Atletico Madrid",
    questionId: "15",
  },
  {
    question:
      "English rock star Elton John was twice the owner of which football club?",
    answers: ["Oxford united", "Brentford", "Millwall", "Watford"],
    correct: "Watford",
    questionId: "16",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which multinational sports wear company is Messi an ambassador for?",
    answers: ["Adidas", "Puma", "Nike", "New balance"],
    correct: "Adidas",
    questionId: "17",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Messi famously retired from international duty in which year before reversing his decision?",
    answers: ["2015", "2018", "2017", "2016"],
    correct: "2016",
    questionId: "18",
  },
  {
    question: "Messi has won a record number of Ballon d'Or awards, how many?",
    answers: ["7", "8", "5", "4"],
    correct: "8",
    questionId: "19",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Portuguese team did Ronaldo play for before signing for Manchester United?",
    answers: ["braga", "Sporting Lisbon", "fc Madiera", "Boavista"],
    correct: "Sporting Lisbon",
    questionId: "20",
  },
];

export default (n = 5) =>
  Promise.resolve(questionBank.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));